# **GABRIEL ATIENZA**

Data Analyst | San Francisco, CA

7 years of experience in varied analytical roles to drive business decision making. Master's Degree holder with excellent analytic and communication skills. Keen attention to detail while keeping track of the bigger picture.

gab.atienza@gmail.com 818-519-9254 /in/gabrielatienza/

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Analyst | GAP Inc

May 2016 - present | San Francisco, CA

- Managed support and development of Supply Chain Management Tools used in all Gap brands (Gap, Old Navy, Banana Republic, Athleta)
- Lessened data issues by proactively working with the data team to analyze effects of impending system changes
- Created testing strategies for the team prior to rollouts of new tools
- Communicated information to a user base of approximately 500 people
- Prioritized high-level issues while still maintaining SLA of all issue resolution
- Worked directly with developers to fix bugs and add functionality
- Utilized Oracle Essbase to ensure accurate inventory plans in multiple markets (Global, US, CA EU, etc.) and levels (Brand, Division, Department, etc.)
- Within 6 months from starting, was tasked to train a new resource in the team after quickly adapting to company's resources and processes

# Finance Analyst | Dream Volts Marketing

Apr 2015 - Jan 2016 | Manila, Philippines

- Effectively communicated key financial indicators with upper management in making key decisions by analyzing and consolidating monthly financial data
- Secured P1.2M of additional funding for future shipments by presenting a Discounted Cash Flow Analysis

# Market Analyst | Philippine Long Distance Telephone Co. (PLDT)

Dec 2011 - Apr 2015 | Manila, Philippines

- Properly identified growth sectors and weak areas in the domestic market; both of which led to increased gross sales by 30 percent
- Created interactive dashboards using SAP Dashboard for Finance, Sales, Marketing, and Engineering
- Developed standards for testing and plan execution, still currently used, for market analysis.
- Designed a company tool in Python for continuous monitoring, data gathering and future analysis of company, subsidiary, and competitor facilities increasing market share to above 55 percent

#### **SKILLS**

- Data Analysis
- Data Dashboard
- Data Cleaning
- Competitive Analysis
- Market Research

#### **TOOLS**

- MS Excel
- Python
- SQL
- Oracle Essbase
- SAP Dashboard Design

#### **EDUCATION**

MS & BS in Applied Mathematics: Major in Mathematical Finance Ateneo De Manila

Ateneo De Manila University Mar 2011